Inventory of the National Cattlemen’s Association records, 1898-2018
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Subject Files, Series VI.
  - Meat Exports to Mexico, 1993 (Box 695)
  - Meat Import Law (General), 1991-1993 (Box 694)
  - Meat Import Law, 1979-1992 (Box 695)
  - Meat Industry Trade Policy Council, 1991 (Box 695)
  - Mexico, 1992-1995 (Box 695)
  - Mexico Live Imports to US, 1984-1991 (Box 695)
  - Mexico - "The Mexican Economy", 1994 (Box 695)
  - Mexico - "The Main Questions on Customs Regarding North American Free Trade Agreement", 1994 (Box 695)
  - San Pedro, 1986 (Box 694)
  - Alan Sobba, 1995 (Box 695)
  - Tenth World Meat Congress Delegate Listing, 1995 (Box 695)
  - USDA - Foreign Ag Service, 1991 (Box 695)
  - USTR (General), 1986-1998 (Box 695)
  - U.S. - Canada Trade, 1986-1993 (Box 695)
  - U.S. - Australia Trade, 1991-1992 (Box 694)
  - U.S. - Japanese Trade, 1991-1992 (Box 694)
  - U.S. - Korea Trade, 1993-1995 (Box 694)
  - U.S. - Soviet Trade, 1990-1995 (Box 694)
  - U.S. Meat Export Federation, 1991-1993 (Box 695)
  - USMEF Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 695)
  - The Wallace Decision, 1991 (Box 695)
  - WTO Dispute Settlement, 1995 (Box 695)
  - 1997 wrap up (Taxpayer Relief Act of 1997) (Box 702)
  - 2002 farm bill conference report (Box 707)
  - Actions for free trade, 1997-2006 (Box 703)
  - AG/Biotech, 1998 (Box 702)
  - AG/Fast Track, 1998 (Box 702)
  - Agricultural Foreign Trade-- GATT, 1987-1989 (Box 703)
  - Agriculture appropriations bills - FY99, 1999 (Box 706)
  - Alan BQ, 1992-1993 (Box 703)
  - Animal ag research, 1997 (Box 707)
  - Animal Disease Risk Assessment, Prevention, and Control Act, 2001 (Box 704)
  - Annual report NCEOA, 1997 (Box 703)
  - Australia, 2002-2003 (Box 703)
  - Australia project 2, 1998 (Box 702)
  - Awards: Membership plaque, 1976 (Box 708)
  - Beef industry food safety council, 1997 (Box 702)
  - Beef inspection, 1992-1993 (Box 704)
  - Beef Reproduction Module #3: Reproductive Losses and Technologies (CD), 2008 (Digital, Folder ahcdm_01713_012)
  - Book: "A Rider, A Roper, and a Heck'uva Windmill Man", 1982 (Box 697)
  - Book: "Anybody Can be Slow" by Van Irvine, 1989 (Box 707)
  - Book: "Courageous Cattlemen", 1990 (Box 697)
  - Book: "Saratoga and Encampment Wyoming", 1990 (Box 697)
  - Book: "Savvy Sayin's", 1987 (Box 697)
  - Book: "Send Fresh Horses", 1987 (Box 697)
  - Book: "The Face of Rural America", 1976 (Box 697)
  - Book: "Weeds of the West", 1999 (Box 698)
  - Book: "Western Rangeland Revisited" by Debra L. Donahue, 1999 (Box 698)
  - Boxed beef working group, 2000 (Box 704)
  - BSE, 2003-2005 (Box 703)
  - BSE - Bibliography for transmissible spongiform encephalopathies, 1996 (Box 705)
  - BSE - bovine spongiform encephalopathy (mad cow disease), 1993-2003 (Box 705)
  - BSE - bovine spongiform encephalopathy (mad cow disease) Dec 23 and CBS Evening News: Mad Cow Disease (DVD), 2003 (Box 705 and Digital, Folder ahcdm_01713_015)
  - BSE - bovine spongiform encephalopathy (mad cow disease) response plan, 1998 (Box 705)
  - BSE - bovine spongiform encephalopathy (mad cow disease), CJD, BSE, NVCJD information, 2001 (Box 705)
  - BSE - Bovine Spongiform Encephalopathy in Great Britain, 1996 (Box 705)
  - BSE - Transmissible spongiform encephalopathy as a zoonotic disease, 2003 (Box 705)
  - BSE manuscript, 2007 (Box 707)
  - BSE- scientific literature review, 2001 (Box 707)
  - CAFTA, 2005 (Box 703)
  - CATL fund, 1995 (Box 698)
  - CATO, 1998 (Box 703)
  - Chile, 2002-2003 (Box 703)
  - Committee hearings of the US House of Representatives, 1988 (Box 699)
  - Conservation, 1992-1993 (Box 704)
  - Department of Health and Human Services: substances prohibited from use in animal food or feed, 2008 (Box 707)
  - Development of USDA's National Animal Identification Program, 2004 (Box 704)
  - E. Coli, 1993 (Box 705)
  - The Ecosystem Approach: Healthy Ecosystems and Sustainable Economies - report of the Interagency Ecosystem Management Task Force, 1996 (Box 698)
  - Environmental stewardship award, 1991 (Box 707)
  - Estate taxes, 1997 (Box 703)
  - EU hormone ban, 1998 (Box 702)
  - EU hormone dispute, 1998-2002 (Box 703)
  - Executive book summaries from the library of Forrest Roberts (CD), undated (Digital, Folder ahcdm_01713_011)
  - Expanded surveill. plan document, 2004 (Box 703)
  - Farm bill, 1995 (Box 702)
  - Fed lands, 1998 (Box 705)
  - Final report - meat inspections (US compared to Europe), 1992 (Box 702)
  - Fluoroquinolone drugs in animals, 1994 (Box 707)
  - Food Disparagement: Are You Next?, 1998 (Box 705)
  - Food safety/Stabenow, 1998 (Box 702)
  - Foodborne pathogens: review of recommendations, 1994-1998 (Box 699)
  - Foot and mouth disease: guidelines for eradication, 1980 (Box 707)
  - Forest service common aud report, 1991 (Box 698)
  - Gen- FTAs, 2006 (Box 703)
  - GIPSA livestock and meat marketing study, 2007 (Box 704)
  - Harvard risk assessment on BSE in US, 2003 (Box 703)
  - Hearing to review the USDA's National Animal Identification System (NAIS), 2004 (Box 704)
  - Heterocyclic amines in foods and their implications to health, 1996 (Box 704)
  - House slaughter, 2008 (Box 704)
  - HR-1 Stimulus (111th), 2008 (Box 704)
  - IMF bailout, 1998 (Box 702)
  - Iron, 1998-1999 (Box 704)
  - ITC testimony US-Australia FTA, 2003 (Box 703)
  - Japan trade, 2005 (Box 703)
  - Land updates, 1997-1998 (Box 698)
  - Lessons on meat, 1991 (Box 699)
  - Livestock grazing on riparian areas, 1990-1996 (Box 698)
  - Livestock Mandatory Price Reporting System, 2001 (Box 704)
  - Meat inspection, 1993-1994 (Box 704)
  - Meat testing and marketing, 1997-2000 (Box 699)
  - NAFTA, 1993-1999 (Box 704)
  - National animal health monitoring system NAHMS (CD), 2010 (Digital, Folder ahcdm_01713_010)
  - Net op loss, 1997 (Box 703)
  - Next Step: implementing the U.S.-Chile free trade agreement, 2003 (Box 703)
  - The North American livestock, meat, and poultry industry, 1997 (Box 697)
  - NPD crest report on restaurant trends, 1996-1997 (Box 704)
  - Nutrition, 1992-1997 (Box 704)
  - O'Melviny & Myers, 1998 (Box 702)
  - Oprah, 1996-1998 (Box 707)
  - Pathogen reduction; Hazard Analysis and Critical Control Point (HACCP) systems, 1996 (Box 704)
  - Paul DeLaney proposal, 1998 (Box 702)
  - Peru, 2005-2006 (Box 703)
  - Policies, 1995-1998 (Box 702)
  - Present situation of national campaign against BSE, 1990-1999 (Box 704)
  - Proposed revisions to grazing regulations on public lands: Final Environmental Impact Statement - Department of the Interior, Bureau of Land Management, 2004 (Box 698)
  - Public Lands Council (PLC), 1979-2006 (Box 705)
  - Public Lands Council (PLC) - Babbitt Law, 1994-1999 (Box 699)
  - Public Lands Council (PLC) - Brimmer 10th circ., 1998-1999 (Box 699)
  - Public Lands Council (PLC) - meetings, 2002 (Box 698)
  - Public Lands Council (PLC) et al. vs Brue Babbitt et al, 1934-1995 (Box 699)
  - Public Lands Council (PLC) internal review, 1986 (Box 698)
  - Public Lands Council (PLC) office expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 698)
  - Public Lands Council annual meeting, 2000 (Box 707)
  - Public Lands Council report - A Beginner's Guide to Cooperating Agency Status, 2012 (Box 698)
  - Public Lands Council, Plaintiffs vs. Bruce Babbit, Defendants, 1993-1999 (Box 699)
  - Public lands I-II, 1979-2002 (Box 698)
  - Public Lands vs. Petitioners (Supreme Court), 1991-1999 (Box 699)
  - Publications: "Persimmon Hill", 1970-1999 (Box 697)
  - Rangeland, 1992 (Box 698)
  - Red meat and cancer, 1997 (Box 704)
  - Request for information- National Animal Identification System (NAIS), 2005 (Box 705)
  - Research needs relative to meat and cancer, 1995 (Box 704)
  - Research needs relative to meat and diets of young and growing children, 1995 (Box 704)
  - Research needs relative to meat and meat lipids and hard disease, 1995 (Box 704)
  - Rick Bourque, 1998 (Box 702)
  - Selenium, 1993-1994 (Box 707)
  - Senate ag approps schedule, 1999 (Box 702)
  - Smart money, 1997 (Box 699)
  - South Korea, 2006 (Box 703)
  - Steve Glaze info, 1997 (Box 703)
  - Strategic platform (conference), 1995 (Box 702)
  - Suspense accounts, 1995-1997 (Box 703)
  - Take the first step, 2007 (Box 703)
  - Tax letters (out), 1998 (Box 702)
  - Tax policy - C. Willingham testimony, 1997 (Box 702)
  - Tax policy - H.R. 1379, 1997 (Box 702)
  - Tax policy - S. 20 (Daschle), 1997 (Box 702)
  - Tax updates, 1998 (Box 702)
  - Technical procedure and organization, 1990-1999 (Box 704)
  - Transmissible Spongiform Encephalopathies in the United States, 2000 (Box 704)
  - Tuberculosis, 1994 (Box 704)
  - U.S. Japan Beef agreement, 1998 (Box 703)
  - USA-BSE situation: imports and surveillance letters NCBA-USDA, 2004 (Box 703)
  - USDA, 1994 (Box 704)
  - USDA/Harvard release BSE report, 2001 (Box 707)
  - US-Japan joint statement, 2004 (Box 703)
  - Value added task force, 1991-1993 (Box 703)
  - Vegetarianism, 1992 (Box 704)
  - Western Watershed Project (WWP) vs. U.S. (BLM) - Battle Creek administrative record, Dunn Carney (4 DVDs), 2012-2014 (Digital, Folder ahcdm_01713_006-009)
  - Western Watershed Project et al vs. U.S. - AR-AZ grazing CE lawsuit Bates index and PDF files (CD), 2012 (Digital, Folder ahcdm_01713_004)
  - Wild horse and burro literature (CD), undated (Digital, Folder ahcdm_01713_005)
  - Wildlife, 2004-2007 (Box 705)
  - Wildlife services, 2000 (Box 707 and Digital, Box ahcdm_01713_016)
  - Wyoming file, 1997-1998 (Box 705)
  - Year in review, 1998 (Box 703)
  - Zinc, 1994-1999 (Box 704)
- Convention Files, Series VII.
  This series concerns the NCA’s annual conventions and mid-year meetings. It consists of correspondence, press releases, printed materials, proceedings, reports, and resolutions.
  - American National Livestock Association - Annual Convention Programs (2 bound volumes), 1971 (Box 688)
  - American National Livestock Association - Annual Convention Speeches (6 bound volumes), 1971, 1977 (Box 689)
  - First National Convention of Cattlemen, November 17, 1884 - invitation and program (Box 469)
  - American National Livestock Association-1st Annual Convention, 1898 (Box 469, Folder 1)
  - American National Livestock Association-9th Annual Convention, 1906 (Box 469, Folder 2)
  - American National Livestock Association-11th Annual Convention, 1908 (Box 469, Folder 3)
  - American National Livestock Association-15th Annual Convention, 1911 (Box 469, Folder 4)
  - American National Livestock Association-17th Annual Convention, 1914 (Box 469, Folder 5)
  - American National Livestock Association-18th Annual Convention, 1915 (Box 469, Folder 6)
  - American National Livestock Association-19th Annual Convention, 1916 (Box 469, Folders 7-8)
  - American National Livestock Association-20th Annual Convention, 1917 (Box 469, Folders 9-11)
  - American National Livestock Association-21st Annual Convention, 1918 (Box 469, Folder 12)
  - American National Livestock Association-22nd Annual Convention, 1919 (Box 470, Folders 1-3)
  - American National Livestock Association-23rd Annual Convention, 1920 (Box 470, Folders 4-5)
  - American National Livestock Association-24th Annual Convention, 1921 (Box 470, Folder 6)
  - American National Livestock Association-25th Annual Convention, 1922 (Box 470, Folder 7)
  - American National Livestock Association-26th Annual Convention, 1923 (Box 470, Folder 8)
  - American National Livestock Association-27th Annual Convention, 1924 (Box 470, Folders 9-11)
  - American National Livestock Association-28th Annual Convention, 1925 (Box 470, Folders 12-13)
  - American National Livestock Association-29th Annual Convention, 1926 (Box 470, Folders 14-16)
  - American National Livestock Association-30th Annual Convention, 1927 (Box 470, Folder 17)
  - American National Livestock Association-31st Annual Convention, 1928 (Box 470, Folder 18)
  - American National Livestock Association-31st Annual Convention, 1928 (Box 471, Folders 1-2)
  - American National Livestock Association-32nd Annual Convention, 1929 (Box 471, Folders 3-4)
  - American National Livestock Association-33rd Annual Convention, 1930 (Box 471, Folders 5-6)
  - American National Livestock Association-34th Annual Convention, 1931 (Box 471, Folders 7-9)
  - American National Livestock Association-35th Annual Convention, 1931-1932 (Box 471, Folders 10-14)
  - American National Livestock Association-36th Annual Convention, 1933 (Box 471, Folders 15-19)
  - American National Livestock Association-36th Annual Convention, 1933 (Box 472, Folders 1-2)
  - American National Livestock Association-37th Annual Convention, 1934 (Box 472, Folders 3-7)
  - American National Livestock Association-38th Annual Convention, 1935 (Box 472, Folder 8)
  - American National Livestock Association-38th Annual Convention, 1935 (Box 473, Folders 1-3)
  - American National Livestock Association-39th Annual Convention, 1936 (Box 473, Folders 4-6)
  - American National Livestock Association-40th Annual Convention, 1937 (Box 473, Folder 7)
  - American National Livestock Association-41st Annual Convention, 1938 (Box 473, Folder 8)
  - American National Livestock Association-40th Annual Convention, 1937 (Box 474, Folders 1-2)
  - American National Livestock Association-41st Annual Convention, 1938 (Box 474, Folders 3-5)
  - American National Livestock Association-42nd Annual Convention, 1939 (Box 474, Folders 6-9)
  - American National Livestock Association-43rd Annual Convention, 1940 (Box 474, Folders 10-12)
  - American National Livestock Association-44th Annual Convention, 1941 (Box 475, Folders 1-3)
  - American National Livestock Association-45th Annual Convention, 1942 (Box 475, Folders 4-6)
  - American National Livestock Association-46th Annual Convention, 1943 (Box 475, Folder 7)
  - American National Livestock Association-46th Annual Convention, 1943 (Box 476, Folder 1)
  - American National Livestock Association-47th Annual Convention, 1944-1945 (Box 476, Folders 2-5)
  - American National Livestock Association-48th Annual Convention, 1945 (Box 476, Folders 6-9)
  - American National Livestock Association-49th Annual Convention, 1946 (Box 476, Folders 10-12)
  - American National Livestock Association-50th Annual Convention, 1947 (Box 476, Folders 13-15)
  - American National Livestock Association-51st Annual Convention, 1948 (Box 477, Folders 1-4)
  - American National Livestock Association-52nd Annual Convention, 1949 (Box 477, Folders 5-7)
  - American National Livestock Association-53rd Annual Convention, 1950 (Box 477, Folders 8-11)
  - American National Livestock Association-53rd Annual Convention, 1950 (Box 478, Folder 1)
  - American National Livestock Association-54th Annual Convention, 1951 (Box 478, Folders 2-5)
  - American National Livestock Association-55th Annual Convention, 1952 (Box 478, Folders 6-10)
  - American National Livestock Association-56th Annual Convention, 1953 (Box 478, Folders 11-12)
  - American National Livestock Association-56th Annual Convention, 1953 (Box 479, Folders 1-2)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-57th Annual Convention, 1953-1954 (Box 479, Folders 3-5)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-58th Annual Convention, 1955 (Box 479, Folders 6-8)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-59th Annual Convention, 1955-1956 (Box 479, Folders 9-13)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-59th Annual Convention, 1955-1956 (Box 480, Folders 1-4)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-60th Annual Convention-Phoenix Arizona, 1955-1957 (Box 480, Folders 5-10)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-60th Annual Convention-Phoenix Arizona, 1956-1957 (Box 481, Folders 1-8)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-61st Annual Convention-Oklahoma City, OK, 1957-1958 (Box 481, Folders 9-10)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-61st Annual Convention-Oklahoma City, OK, 1957-1958 (Box 482, Folders 1-9)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-62nd Annual Convention-Omaha, NE, 1956-1959 (Box 482, Folders 10-13)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-62nd Annual Convention-Omaha, NE, 1958-1959 (Box 483, Folders 1-7)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-62nd Annual Convention-Omaha, NE, 1957-1959 (Box 484, Folders 1-12)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-63rd Annual Convention-Dallas, TX, 1959 (Box 484, Folder 13)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-63rd Annual Convention-Dallas, TX, 1959-1960 (Box 485, Folders 1-10)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-63rd Annual Convention-Dallas, TX, 1959-1960 (Box 486, Folders 1-7)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-64th Annual Convention, 1960-1961 (Box 486, Folders 8-10)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-64th Annual Convention, 1960-1961 (Box 487, Folders 1-5)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-64th Annual Convention, 1960-1961 (Box 488, Folders 1-6)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-65th Annual Convention-Tampa, FL, 1960-1962 (Box 488, Folders 7-11)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-65th Annual Convention-Tampa, FL, 1960-1962 (Box 489, Folders 1-11)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-65th Annual Convention-Tampa, FL, 1961-1962 (Box 490, Folders 1-7)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-66th Annual Convention, Las Vegas, NV, 1961-1962 (Box 490, Folder 8)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-66th Annual Convention, Las Vegas, NV, 1962-1963 (Box 491, Folders 1-7)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-66th Annual Convention, Las Vegas, NV, 1962-1963 (Box 492, Folders 1-10)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-67th Annual Convention, Memphis, TN, 1962-1964 (Box 492, Folders 11-15)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-67th Annual Convention, Memphis, TN, 1962-1964 (Box 493, Folders 1-12)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-67th Annual Convention, Memphis, TN, 1962-1964 (Box 494, Folders 1-7)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-68th Annual Convention, Portland, OR, 1963-1965 (Box 494, Folders 8-11)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-68th Annual Convention, Portland, OR, 1964-1965 (Box 495, Folders 1-7)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-69th Annual Convention, Kansas City, MO, 1964-1966 (Box 495, Folders 8-9)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-69th Annual Convention, Kansas City, MO, 1964-1966 (Box 496, Folders 1-5)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-70th Annual Convention, 1965-1967 (Box 496, Folders 6-11)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-71st Annual Convention, 1967-1968 (Box 496, Folders 12-16)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-72nd Annual Convention, 1969 (Box 496, Folder 17)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-71st Annual Convention, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1969 (Box 496, Folder 18)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-75th Annual Convention, 1972 (Box 496, Folder 19)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-83rd Annual Convention, 1980 (Box 496, Folder 20)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-84th Annual Convention, 1980-1981 (Box 496, Folders 21-25)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-85th Annual Convention, 1981-1982 (Box 496, Folder 26)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-85th Annual Convention, 1981-1982 (Box 497, Folders 1-2)
  - American National Cattlemen’s Association-91st Annual Convention, 1988 (Box 497, Folder 3)
  - Future Conventions, 1960-1965 (Box 497, Folders 4-8)
  - Future Conventions, 1966-1969 (Box 498, Folders 1-3)
  - American National Livestock Association-Mid-Year Meetings, 1921, 1922, 1933 (Box 498, Folders 4-7)
  - Miscellaneous Reservations, 1956-1968 (Box 498, Folder 8)
  - 47th Annual Convention, Denver, CO, 1944 (Box 499, Folder 1)
  - 48th Annual Convention, Denver, CO, 1945 (Box 499, Folder 2)
  - 49th Annual Convention, Denver, CO, 1946 (Box 499, Folders 3-4)
  - 50th Annual Convention, Phoenix, AZ, 1947 (Box 499, Folders 5-6)
  - 51st Annual Convention, Boise, ID, 1948 (Box 499, Folders 7-8)
  - 52nd Annual Convention, North Platte, NE, 1949 (Box 499, Folders 9-10)
  - 53rd Annual Convention, Miami, FL, 1950 (Box 499, Folders 11-12)
  - 54th Annual Convention, San Francisco, CA, 1951 (Box 499, Folder 13)
  - 72nd Annual Convention, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1967-1968 (Box 499, Folder 14)
  - 73rd Annual Convention, Washington D.C., 1969 (Box 499, Folder 15)
  - 74th Annual Convention, Las Vegas, NV, 1970-1971 (Box 499, Folder 16)
  - 75th Annual Convention, 1972 (Box 499, Folder 17)
  - 83rd Annual Convention, 1980 (Box 499, Folders 18-22)
  - 84th Annual Convention, 1980-1981 (Box 499, Folders 23-24)
  - 85th Annual Convention, 1980-1982 (Box 499, Folders 25-35)
  - 86th Annual Convention, 1982-1983 (Box 500, Folders 1-3)
  - 87th Annual Convention, 1983-1984 (Box 500, Folders 4-5)
  - 88th Annual Convention, 1984-1985 (Box 500, Folders 6-8)
  - 89th Annual Convention, 1985-1986 (Box 500, Folders 9-13)
  - 90th Annual Convention, 1986-1987 (Box 500, Folders 14-19)
  - Future Convention, 1985 (Box 500, Folder 20)
  - 35th Annual Convention, San Antonio, TX, 1932 (Box 500, Folders 21-22)
  - 36th Annual Convention, Ogden, Utah, 1933 (Box 500, Folder 23)
  - 37th Annual Convention, Albuquerque, NM, 1934 (Box 500, Folders 24-25)
  - 40th Annual Convention, El Paso, TX, 1937 (Box 500, Folder 26)
  - 55th Annual Convention, Fort Worth, TX, 1952 (Box 500, Folder 27)
  - 56th Annual Convention, Kansas City, MO, 1953 (Box 500, Folder 28)
  - 57th Annual Convention, Colorado Springs, CO, 1954 (Box 500, Folders 29-30)
  - 58th Annual Convention, Reno, NV, 1955 (Box 500, Folder 31)
  - 59th Annual Convention, New Orleans, LA, 1956 (Box 500, Folders 32-33)
  - 60th Annual Convention, Phoenix, AZ, 1957 (Box 500, Folders 34-35)
  - 61st Annual Convention, Oklahoma City, OK, 1958 (Box 501, Folders 1-3)
  - 62nd Annual Convention, Omaha, NE, 1959 (Box 501, Folders 4-5)
  - 63rd Annual Convention, Dallas, TX, 1960 (Box 501, Folders 6-7)
  - 65th Annual Convention, Tampa, FL, 1962 (Box 501, Folders 8-9)
  - 68th Annual Convention, Portland, OR, 1965 (Box 501, Folder 10)
  - 66th Annual Convention, Las Vegas, NV, 1963 (Box 501, Folder 11)
  - 68th Annual Convention, Portland, OR, 1965 (Box 501, Folder 12)
  - 69th Annual Convention, Kansas City, MO, 1966 (Box 501, Folder 13)
  - 71st Annual Convention, Oklahoma City, OK, 1968 (Box 501, Folder 14)
  - 73rd Annual Convention, Washington D.C., 1970 (Box 501, Folder 15)
  - 71st Annual Convention, Oklahoma City, OK, 1968 (Box 501, Folder 16)
  - 54th Annual Convention, San Francisco, CA, 1951 (Box 502, Folder 1)
  - 39th Annual Convention, Phoenix, AZ, 1936 (Box 502, Folder 2)
  - 41st Annual Convention, Cheyenne, WY, 1938 (Box 502, Folder 3)
  - 42nd Annual Convention, San Francisco, CA, 1939 (Box 502, Folder 4)
  - 44th Annual Convention, Fort Worth, TX, 1941 (Box 502, Folder 5)
  - 45th Annual Convention, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1942 (Box 502, Folders 6-7)
  - 46th Annual Convention, Denver, CO, 1943 (Box 502, Folders 8-9)
  - 47th Annual Convention, Denver, CO, 1944 (Box 502, Folder 10)
  - 72nd Annual Convention, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1969 (Box 502, Folder 11)
  - 76th Annual Convention, San Antonio, TX, 1972-1973 (Box 502, Folder 12)
  - 77th Annual Convention, San Diego, CA, 1973-1974 (Box 502, Folder 13)
  - 43rd Annual Convention, Denver, CO, 1940 (Box 503, Folders 1-2)
  - 44th Annual Convention, Fort Worth, TX, 1941 (Box 503, Folder 3)
  - 66th Annual Convention, Las Vegas, NV, 1963 (Box 503, Folders 4-5)
  - 67th Annual Convention, Memphis, TN, 1964 (Box 503, Folders 6-7)
  - 68th Annual Convention, Portland, OR, 1965 (Box 503, Folder 8)
  - 69th Annual Convention, Kansas City, MO, 1966 (Box 503, Folders 9-10)
  - 70th Annual Convention, Colorado Springs, CO, 1967 (Box 503, Folders 11-12)
  - 71st Annual Convention, Oklahoma City, OK, 1967-1968 (Box 503, Folder 13)
  - 74th Annual Convention, 1971 (Box 503, Folder 14)